Safe is never sex. It’s dangerous.
The Hot Spot is a romance, crime, thriller film directed by Dennis Hopper.
Upon arriving to a small town, a drifter quickly gets into trouble with the
local authorities — and the local women — after he robs a bank.
Harry Madox, played by Don Johnson.
Dolly Harshaw, played by Virginia Madsen.
Gloria Harper, played by Jennifer Connelly.
Lon Gulick, played by Charles Martin Smith.
Frank Sutton, played by William Sadler.
George Harshaw, played by Jerry Hardin.
The Hot Spot is a 1990 American neo-noir romantic thriller film directed by Dennis Hopper, based on
the 1953 novel Hell Hath No Fury by Charles Williams, who also co-wrote the screenplay.
It stars Don Johnson, Virginia Madsen, and Jennifer Connelly, and features a score by Jack Nitzsche played by
John Lee Hooker, Miles Davis, Taj Mahal, Roy Rogers, Tim Drummond, and drummer Earl Palmer.
The film explores themes of paradise, photographer, smoking, bank robber, arson.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.